[{
    "theme": "⏰ Gramática – El presente",
    "langread": "en",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "What do you do during the weekend?",
            "answers": ["haces"]
        },
        {
            "question": "The weekend",
            "answers": ["el fin de semana"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Does the sun shine?",
            "answers": ["hace"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you work in the restaurant?",
            "answers": ["trabajas"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you (formal) work in the restaurant?",
            "answers": ["trabaja"]
        },
        {
            "question": "I work.",
            "answers": ["trabajo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Does Carla work?",
            "answers": ["trabaja"]
        },
        {
            "question": "We work.",
            "answers": ["trabajamos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "You all (informal) work.",
            "answers": ["trabajáis"]
        },
        {
            "question": "They work.",
            "answers": ["trabajan"]
        },
        {
            "question": "I dance.",
            "answers": ["bailo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "You dance.",
            "answers": ["bailas"]
        },
        {
            "question": "He or she dances.",
            "answers": ["baila"]
        },
        {
            "question": "We dance.",
            "answers": ["bailamos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "You all (informal) dance.",
            "answers": ["bailáis"]
        },
        {
            "question": "They dance.",
            "answers": ["bailan"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Infinitive of 'to spend time'.",
            "answers": ["pasar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "I spend time with my family.",
            "answers": ["paso"]
        },
        {
            "question": "You spend (time).",
            "answers": ["pasas"]
        },
        {
            "question": "He/She spends (time).",
            "answers": ["pasa"]
        },
        {
            "question": "We spend (time).",
            "answers": ["pasamos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "You all spend (time).",
            "answers": ["pasáis"]
        },
        {
            "question": "They spend (time).",
            "answers": ["pasan"]
        },
        {
            "question": "I speak with my friends.",
            "answers": ["hablo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "You speak with your friends.",
            "answers": ["hablas"]
        },
        {
            "question": "He/She speaks.",
            "answers": ["habla"]
        },
        {
            "question": "We speak.",
            "answers": ["hablamos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "You all speak.",
            "answers": ["habláis"]
        },
        {
            "question": "They speak.",
            "answers": ["hablan"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Infinitive of 'to chat'.",
            "answers": ["charlar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "I chat.",
            "answers": ["charlo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "You chat.",
            "answers": ["charlas"]
        },
        {
            "question": "He/She chats.",
            "answers": ["charla"]
        },
        {
            "question": "We chat.",
            "answers": ["charlamos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "You all chat.",
            "answers": ["charláis"]
        },
        {
            "question": "They chat.",
            "answers": ["charlan"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Infinitive of 'to talk' (used in Latin America).",
            "answers": ["platicar"]
        }
    ]
}]
